<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="read_and_accept">"I have read and accept "</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="reservation_instructions">Reservation Instructions</string>
    <string name="reservation_time_change_terms">Modify appointment or cancel travel</string>
    <string name="payment_conditions">Reservation and online payment</string>
    <string name="reservation_instructions_details">The ticket is valid for travel on the service specified in it and subject to restrictions or data written on it upon issuance such as service type, travel date, day, specified hour, price and all other data\n The traveler must make sure before booking the itinerary, departure time and station The ride and services for each bus, the name of the land transport bus company, and the meaning of the payment is that you are sure and fully aware of all the aforementioned information \n You must keep your ticket as an immediate receipt during the trip and you must present it in the event that it is requested for examination\n If your ticket is not with you On the bus, and it turns out that you did not book in advance, you must pay the value of another ticket according to the availability of seats, and then the ticket will be purchased through the driver only with the payment of the prescribed fine for that.\nThe English Company for Transport and Trips will not replace any lost or stolen tickets. Being able to issue a replacement for a lost ticket, and in case the traveler’s ownership is proven, the fine will be paid. If there are empty seats\nIn the event of an increase or decrease in the announced ticket prices after purchasing the ticket, the company is not entitled to ask the company to pay or refund the price difference\n and discount tickets for shows cannot be returned\nThe driver can issue a ticket to the passenger at the time of departure, in case Availability of vacant seats on the bus belonging to the driver or the English company for transport and trips The English company for transport and trips has the right to amend the daily trip schedule or amend ticket prices without prior notice with the possibility of communicating with the passenger about adjusting the travel date in sufficient time.</string>
    <string name="global_terms_details">The passenger must be at the departure station 30 minutes before the scheduled time of the trip\n to allow time for boarding procedures on the bus and to prevent any delay\nThe bus stops only picking up/unloading passengers at the official stations according to the line The announced course of the trip\nArrival at the departure station before the flight date is the sole responsibility of the traveler, and in the event that the traveler does not catch up with the time of the trip, the ticket is considered canceled and he is not entitled to request a refund of any return or compensation\nThe bus is not allowed to return to the travel station or the assembly point again To pick up passengers who are late for the flight after the bus has moved on time\n a flight may be canceled or rescheduled and this may be as a result of factors beyond the company’s control such as weather, road accidents, security instructions, emergency technical problems or any other force majeure circumstances and in this In the case, the traveler has the right to claim compensation for the value of the ticket from the English company for transportation and trips with a deduction of a percentage from the value of the ticket if the English company for transportation and trips is found. D is specified due to the delay in the date of departure or arrival\n and it is not entitled to claim any compensation or return in the event of a delay of an hour or less from the scheduled time of the trip\n Display screens or any equipment in the bus salon, and the traveler bears the value of damages and damages, as well as legal liability in the event he refuses the compensation specified by the company. Official channels such as the company’s branch or the official website on the Internet or the hotline, and within five days from the date of arrival, the complaint will be investigated and return to the traveler within 30 days, provided that the travel ticket is kept, as it is considered a contract between the traveler and the English company for transport and trips</string>
    <string name="global_terms">General Terms</string>
    <string name="traveling_terms">Travel Instructions</string>
    <string name="traveling_terms_details">Make sure you are on the correct bus: the passenger must make sure that he is on the correct bus heading to the exact place he booked</string>
    <string name="rest_terms_details">In the event of a stop at the rest stops, you must return to the bus at the exact time available for the break\n and the company is not required to delay the bus\'s departure time to wait for a passenger\n and is not entitled to claim any compensation or any additional expenses that may occur As a result of the passenger\'s failure to leave the bus from the rest site</string>
    <string name="seat_belt_terms_details">The traveler is legally required to wear the seatbelt available in the seat at all times during the flight\n Smoking is prohibited either on the bus or at the station. Based on the fact that there is no evidence about the safety of electronic cigarettes, we ask our valued customers not to use them either. While on board the buses of the English Company for Transport and Trips</string>
    <string name="children_travelling_terms_details">Children from 4 years old will be issued a full ticket\n Children under 4 years old are not assigned a seat and no transportation fee will be charged provided they are accompanied by their parents</string>
    <string name="bags_terms">Bags and Shipping</string>
    <string name="seat_belt_terms">seat belts</string>
    <string name="rest_terms">stop for a break</string>
    <string name="children_travelling_terms">Children\'s travel</string>
    <string name="bags_terms_details">Bags are loaded onto the bus at the responsibility of their owners and are subject to the standard provisions for land transport. Each passenger is allowed to have 2 medium-sized bags, provided that the total weight does not exceed 35 kg, in addition to a small handbag that can be placed in the designated rack on the bus. At the top of the chairs or in the space below the passenger seat\nShipping charges may apply to any additional bag or shipment with the passenger according to the shipping fees established at the travel stations, and the passenger must pay the value due before the date of travel on the bus. Receiving the label of each bag or shipment belonging to it and the source from the reservation offices at the travel station\n private The English Company for Transport and Trips The English Company for Transportation and Trips is not responsible for the passengers’ personal belongings, loss or damage inside the bus or the boarding station, and this is the responsibility of the passenger\n if any Bag or belongings belonging to another passenger on the bus or at the station, the passenger must deliver it immediately</string>
    <string name="payment_terms_details">The reservation will be canceled from the site or the English company\'s application for transport and trips on the mobile automatically in the event of non-payment within two hours of booking time with Fawry service or similar payment companies, knowing that the passenger will be placed in the black list that It belongs to the company if this procedure is done more than three times \n In the case of electronic reservation, please make sure of all the data that appears on the reservation screen of the website or the private mobile application. On the e-mail if the inspector or the reservation officer asks him \n The maximum number of tickets for reservation is 8 tickets only, distributed on the go and back. In the event that the price of the tickets is returned for reasons or compelling circumstances from the English company for transport and trips, the value of the tickets shall be returned to the customer’s balance on the discount card of his wallet </string>
    <string name="reservation_time_change_terms_details">In the event of no-show for the flight specified in the ticket, the ticket becomes void and the traveler has no right to request a refund of the ticket value or use it on another flight. The request for a refund of a non-existent, lost or stolen ticket is not permitted if it is found that the traveler has not booked. \nIt is not right to request a refund of the value of a ticket paid in cash or through various payment methods, provided that the value due is refunded to the customer\'s balance on his wallet discount card, in accordance with the investment law for online purchase \nThe ticket cannot be sold to others</string>
    <string name="travelling_instructions">Travel instructions</string>
    <string name="accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="must_accept_terms">You must accept Terms And Conditions</string>
</resources>